fanbase.com 2015-12-22

# Privacy Policy – Fanbase

**Last Revised: April 30, 2014**

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Fanbase Media, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (“ **Fanbase** “). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website and other online products and services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “ **Services** “) or when you otherwise interact with us.

**Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**Collection of Information**

**Information You Provide Us.** We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Services, submit content, create your member profile, participate in surveys, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address and any other information you choose to provide.  If you are also a subject of a Sports Profile (as defined in the Terms of Service), we may include publicly available information about you on the Sports Profile.

**Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services.** When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

  * **Log Information:**   We log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
  * **Device Information:   **We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:**   We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

**Information We Collect From Other Sources**

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and friends lists, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such social media site.

**Use of Information**

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests;
  * Communicate with you about services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by Fanbase and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

Fanbase is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

**Sharing of Information**

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Fanbase or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**Social Sharing Features**

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

**Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others**

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Fanbase and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

**Security**

Fanbase takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**Your Choices**

**Account Information.** You may update, correct or delete information connected with your member account at any time by logging into your member account or emailing us with your request at [privacy@fanbase.com](mailto:privacy@fanbase.com "mailto:privacy@fanbase.com"). If you wish to deactivate your account, you may do so at any time by using the tools in your member account or by contacting us at [help@fanbase.com](mailto:help@fanbase.com "mailto:help@fanbase.com"), but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

**Cookies.** Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

**Promotional Communications.** You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or messages from Fanbase by following the instructions in those emails or messages or by using the tools in your member account. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing service relationship.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@fanbase.com](mailto:privacy@fanbase.com "mailto:privacy@fanbase.com").
